<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>BillTollett.com - Misc</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2018-02-17T21:29:00-10:00</updated><entry><title>What? Again with the writing?</title><link href="/what-again-with-the-writing.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-02-17T20:51:00-10:00</published><updated>2018-02-17T21:29:00-10:00</updated><author><name>Bill Tollett</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-02-17:/what-again-with-the-writing.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It's that time again where every few years I feel like there should be something on my site. The last time this happened, I was starting to think I should be looking for a new job and so wanted to put something up on the web that talked about what …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It's that time again where every few years I feel like there should be something on my site. The last time this happened, I was starting to think I should be looking for a new job and so wanted to put something up on the web that talked about what I'd been working on as well as various other things I was interested in. That's not the case this time -- I love my job -- and anyways I think I got all of one post published before I stopped. Will things be different this time? Stay tuned to find out...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be doing some different stuff this time around. For one thing, my wife and I attempt to try a new cocktail recipe every Friday (you can find past cocktails displayed in my &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/billt721"&gt;twitter feed&lt;/a&gt;). I briefly considered making the Cocktail Friday stuff its own site, but that didn't last long. Better to put it all here and encourage me to actually post stuff. The other thing I'd like to do here is baseball writing. I've long wanted to get into the stats-based baseball writing community, but being a fan of the Mariners has really made it difficult to stay enthused about the sport for more than a month or two at the beginning of every season. This year likely won't be any different, but I have a few ideas for articles that I'd like to do. I also have a horse racing study I'd like to do, but that's less likely to get finished given how difficult it is to obtain good horse racing data in sufficient quantities to do anything interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there it is: the first post on my newly active again site. Will it last? Who knows. Check back in a month and see if this post is still the only thing on the site.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="first"></category><category term="misc"></category></entry></feed>